ARUN PRASAD V

Frontend Developer

I am a 23-year-old Frontend Developer who develops clean, appealing, and functional interfaces. And I enjoy creating things that live on the internet. My main focus these days is building accessible, inclusive products and digital experiences for the users.

EXPERIENCE

INFOSYS BANGALORE

System Engineer, Jan 2022 - Present

Frontend developer at Infosys

MEGAM SOLUTIONS CHENNAI

Frontend Developer, Jan 2021 - Jan 2022

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Created and Maintained 3 Websites for IIT Madras (re-design, seasonal updates)
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Worked in an Agile, Collaborative environment to receive design requirements, peer programs, and test websites

EDUCATION

VAIGAI COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING MADURAI

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

2016 - 2020

CATHY MATRICULATION HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL MADURAI

BOTH 10TH AND 12TH STANDARD

Portfolio

<u>arunprasadvel21@gmail.com</u>

ໍາດ <u>LinkedIn</u>

491 9789198372

Tamil Nadu, India

LANGUAGES

HTML

CSS (SASS, Tailwind CSS)

JavaScript

MySQL

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

Bootstrap

React

HUGO

Raphael JS

Next JS

TOOLS

Git

Notion

Slack

Google Analytics

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Listening Music

Tech Gadgets